Hello hello everyone today I will give you a review of Star Health
Insurance's new product Star Health
Premier Insurance Policy
last one must for health that some new
products are in the market which are very
good and this product also looks quite good
so for those people who want
mediclaim insurance
policy there is no limit on maximum entries
and it has very good amazing
features welcome to this channel
on this channel we share regular insurance and
investment required information
if you have any question you can
ask us in the comment section you can
whatsapp and if you liked the video
then like and subscribe the video
minimum entry
cannot be subscribed and if i have entered there are
no limitations pendant child
plan can be added to it
subscribe both are available in individual
family floater
policy if appointed then you can
subscribe your
new born baby then after 90 you
can add in this policy subscribe
any policy has medical checkup that means you have to get
medical done before taking it this is the thing  If you
do this, then the minimum
subscription is of Rs 1 crore and
whichever folder you choose, you can
get the maximum subscription. Room rent and
productive work can be done up
to a maximum of 20 days. Free
hospitalization is 60 days. Post
hospitalization is an ingredient.
Talking about road ambulance, whatever
your road ambulance
expenses are, the company bears it, you
can apply for the ambulance, which can be
subscribed for Rs 2.5 crore. Talking about width, you
can subscribe to this treatment and this treatment in
Ayurveda, Siddha, Unani. In this product, you
can get up-to-the-minute treatment. If you get
Aloe Vera done in this, then it should be a
government hospital, it should be
government approved. Subscribe to this
product.
Like and subscribe.
Thankfully, the payment which the hospital claims is due to this
product. This product has inbuilt memory
treatment, which means that tomorrow
if someone faces such a situation that the
policy holder cannot get treatment done in the hospital, if it is
not available here, then he can get
treatment done from his home. You
can subscribe.
3D treatment is compulsory in this, this should be  You
can also subscribe to the product. The
subscription is
available only for policy holders. The Chinese
application is available on Star Power and
you can also check it on the customer portal,
which is available for UK customers. It is
not available for group insurance policies. The British subscription is available, which
can be subscribed to.
Now we can spend up to ₹5,000 on this. If the
policy holder requires any surgery due to obesity, then it should be
Ghr
or Plus and
if you
subscribe and
subscribe, you can also avail the
benefit of quarterly bariatric surgery. The
next point is the no-claim bonus. In this plan, there is
a no-claim bonus
which will increase
to the maximum. If you click, then at the same
speed at which it increases, you
can subscribe to the product and the flu situation treatment. You can
subscribe if you
can subscribe and you can spend ₹4,000 in the family floater
if you combine MS Word
and  If you have an individual policy then
you can claim up to ₹4000 and
Rs.6000 in family floater If
you have another Rs.30 lakh then you can
subscribe for ₹500 in individual and Rs.60 in family floater You
can subscribe up to ₹5000 and Rs.7000
in family floater You can
subscribe up to ₹5000 and Rs.7000 in family floater
Treatment
₹3000
appointed policy ₹4000
for appointment ₹60
[Music]
Shift in like this amendment on phase
plane and for family floater from
75 lakh crore for 7 minutes for
individual to ₹100 for family floater You
can claim up to ₹1000
You can subscribe for neck point home treatment
which
is available in some specific conditions
Talking about payment, this product
Shyam Ko payment  If you take flaxseed after 65 years of age, then you
can subscribe to Yuvraj and
if you
can subscribe on the maximum limit, then the
next point is that you can get a discount on the premium
if you
submit your health checkup when you
take the policy, at that time you can get a discount of two sons,
on renewal also a discount of Rs. 100 is applicable,
that is
subscribe PM
report
subscribe
complete urine examination
product
divided in product
Delhi Faridabad Gurgaon Noida Mumbai
Surat
Extra, if we talk about second rest of India, then
you can do it for 3 years together at a
minimum, you
get a subscription or if you take it together you
get a discount of Rs. 11.25, if we talk about waiting period, then for
any kind of feeling, there is a
waiting period of 30 days for critical illness, for specific diseases like
cataract stone piler,
before taking the waiting period for the extra,
if you have any disease, then you will have to do a
waiting period of 2 years for the appointer, please
subscribe if you
liked the video  Please
like and subscribe to our channel,
thank you for watching.